dizzler.com 2009-12-21

# Free Music & Videos, Music Lyrics, Free music without download

Dizzler understands that privacy is extremely important to you and is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains how IDV8, Inc. ("Dizzler") collects and uses personally identifiable information about visitors to the site and users of the service. By visiting the Dizzler site or using its services, you are accepting the practices outline in this Privacy Policy. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Dizzler does not own or control, or to individuals that Dizzler does not employ or manage. 

_The information Dizzler collects_   
Dizzler collects non-personally identifiable information when you visit our website ([www.Dizzler.com](http://www.dizzler.com/)). This data includes your IP address, the IP address and URL of the Website that sent you to the Dizzler main page, browser cookie and browser type. This data is automatically recorded in our server logs and is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the Dizzler website and services.   
When you use Dizzler services and register for Dizzler, we collect additional information such as your name, mobile phone number, mobile phone device information and network carrier information. We also collect any optional information you choose to enter like email address, location information (such as address, zip code, and country), gender and age.  
When you connect to the Dizzler services on your mobile device, if your mobile phone service provider uniquely identifies the device, Dizzler will receive this information. Dizzler may use your unique mobile device identification information to offer you extended services and/or functionality. Some mobile phone service providers are required to operate a system that will record the physical location of devices that use their service. Depending on the mobile phone service provider, Dizzler may automatically receive this information.  
When you visit the Dizzler site, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Dizzler uses both session cookies - cookies that expire after you close your browser - and persistent cookies - cookies that can be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our website (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of Dizzler's most attractive features.  
Dizzler members can invite friends to join the service and preview content by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. Dizzler stores the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added as Friends of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the invitations. 

_How Dizzler uses your personal information_   
Dizzler uses your personal information to operate, maintain and provide you with the features and functionality of the Dizzler site and services. Dizzler uses your mobile phone number to deliver the mobile content you create and other content you request.   
Additionally, Dizzler may, from time to time, use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or subsequently opt-out. We may also use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Dizzler service changes or for customer service purposes).   
Dizzler uses personally identifiable and certain non-personally identifiable information so that:

  * You will not have to re-enter information during your visit or the next time you visit the Dizzler site 
  * We can improve the quality and design of our website and services and to create new features and functionality 
  * We can monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns 
  * We can monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc. 

Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose online (on the Dizzler site, in our discussion, rating and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other users when you upload contents or send messages from the Dizzler site. Others can contact you as a result of messages you send. Any text, audio, image or other content posted at the direction of users onto the Dizzler site becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy. In addition, Dizzler may use comments posted in public areas about the Dizzler site or services for editorial purposes or in promotional, advertising or marketing materials. Users who submit such comments in these public places on the site grant a non-exclusive, perpetual, irrevocable, transferable, royalty-free license to Dizzler to transmit, publicly display, publicly perform, reproduce, edit, translate and reformat and otherwise use such public information. 

_Information Sharing and Disclosure_   
Dizzler may also share your information in cases where we believe that disclosure is necessary to: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Dizzler, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Dizzler Terms of Use or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. Â Dizzler reserves the right to transfer personal information upon a transfer or sale to another entity of all or substantially all of Dizzler's stock or assets.

Â  _Security of Your Personal Information_  
Your Dizzler account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to work to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer. We use industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software to protect the security of your personal information during transmission, which encrypts all of the information you input. Only Dizzler employees who need personal information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices.  
_Your ability to Edit your Account Information and Preferences_   
You may edit or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by logging into your account and accessing your My Zoo page. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from Dizzler. Please note that content uploaded by Users to Dizzler cannot be removed. For your privacy and security, we request a unique password to verify your identity before granting you profile access in order to make corrections or changes. 

_International Users_   
Dizzler site is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to users in the United States. If you are a user accessing the Dizzler site from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Dizzler site, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you expressly consent to that transfer.

_Links to other sites_   
As part of the Dizzler service, we may provide links to other websites and products. If you choose to visit a third party website or use its products or services, please be aware that the third party's privacy policy, not this Privacy Policy, will be in effect. Please review the privacy policies of these sites in order to understand their privacy policies and data collection practices. Dizzler is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of these websites.

_Children under age 13_   
Dizzler understands the importance of protecting the privacy of children under 13 years of age. Therefore, Dizzler does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information from persons under 13 years of age. Further, no part of our website or service is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Dizzler site or services at any time or in any manner. 

_Changes to our Privacy Policy_   
From time to time, Dizzler may make changes to this Privacy Policy at its sole discretion. If we make changes, we will post them on our site. Please revisit this page to stay informed of the current policy and any changes. Any changes will be reflected in the "effective date" below. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. 

_Conditions of Use_   
If you decide to visit the Dizzler site or use the Dizzler services, your visit and/or use and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of Arizona state law.

_Questions about our Privacy Policy_

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

IDV8, Inc.  
15550 N 84th Street, Suite 105  
Scottsdale, AZ 85086  

Effective date: June 01, 2008
